

# **Parth Patel**

# Frond end Backend | Web Develope (MERN)

I am MERN developer, As a MERN developer, you have the skills and expertise to design, develop, and maintain web applications that leverage these technologies. Your role likely involves tasks such as database design, server-side programming, API development, frontend development, and ensuring the overall performance and functionality of web applications.

#### **Contact Info**

9924069097

**M** patelparth4656@gmail.com

https://raja2282001.github.io/Parth -cv/public\_html/index.html

### **Education**

SILVER OAK COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING 2019-2023

Mangaldeep Higher Secondary School 2017-2019

## **Skills**

## Front End Development

**HTML** 

CSS

**JAVASCRIPT** 

**REACTJS** 

#### **Back End Development**

NODEJS

EXPRESSJS

MONGODB

# **Work Experience**

- FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

  Qubeta Technolab (07/2022 08/2022)

  During his internship he has demonstrated his skills with self-motivation to learn new skills. His performance exceeded our expectations and he was able to complete the project on time
- FRONT-END-BACKEND WEB DEVELOPER
  Arth Infosoft Pvt. Ltd (01/2023-04/2023)
  The MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js)
  stack has revolutionized web development by
  providing a comprehensive set of technologies for
  building robust and scalable applications
- Current WokingOn RNK It Solutions (M E R N)
   04/2023-Present

   RNK IT Solutions, we are passionate about
   transforming your digital visioninto reality.

#### **For More Information**



This Barcode Redirecto to My Personal Website